

Contact Info:

Email: dkirigha18@gmail.com

Phone: +254707256013 Location: Nyeri, Kenya

LinkedIn: linkedin GitHub: github

Skills:

JavaScript, TypeScript, NodeJS, ReactJs, HTML5, CSS3, PostgreSQL, GraphQL, Tailwind

Tools:

Docker, Github, AWS,

Education

Computer Science Karatina University 08/2016 - 11/2020, Computer Science

Achievements

Improved time performance in querying the SQL server (08/2021 - 12/2021)

Improved query performance to the SQL server database by writing stored procedures that took less time to get results from the database.

Languages:

English: Full Professional Proficiency Kiswahili: Full Professional Proficiency

Samuel Kirigha

Software Developer

Profile

Am a passionate, open-minded, and collaborative software developer with experience in writing clean and testable code. I love the challenging nature of software engineering and strongly believe that with discipline and focus we can achieve anything. I am always updated with the latest development in the software development world to be always on the forefront of the latest trends in terms of my skills.

Work Experience

Software Developer at TheJitu.com 01/12/2021 - Present

Implement software solutions that leverage the Rainfocus platform to deliver the best events, conferences, and meetings.

Implement web portals and pages for clients holding virtual and physical events.

Training the Interns and exposing them to real-world projects

Software Developer Intern at TheJitu.com 09/08/2021 - 01/12/2022

Went through the training program an Nodejs, Reactjs, SQL, Docker, and AWS.

Testing and writing reports on the software being developed.

Personal Projects

Project Management System (09/2021 - 10/2021)

A system where the admin can add a new project and its tasks and assign new users to projects giving them specific tasks to handle. All other users can not add a

Interests

Reading tech articles and attending tech events
Writing clean JavaScript code
Watching football
Playing pool
Hiking

project or a task but can view the projects and tasks they are working on.

Bright Events API (05/2021 - 07/2021)

An API where users can create events with date and location/venue, add guests. Manage the event in respect to who is allowed to attend, the location of the event and the venue.

Parcel Sending Services. (12/2021 - Present)

A system to be used by parcel sending companies where the user sending the parcel has access to the system with all the parcel details. He/she receives a notification when the parcel departs the start location and can track the current location of the parcel. Upon delivery, the user gets notified the parcel has arrived.